# ANTHONY YONTA - アンソニー ヨンタ

1248 WALLACE STREET, RICHMOND, VA 23220

H: 804-317-8646 | tyonta@huntonak.com

PORTFOLIO | https://arthidon.github.io/Bootstrap-Portfolio/index.html

# PROFESSIONAL SUMMARY

Seasoned I.T. professional with more than 12 years of experience in fast-paced clientoriented team environments. Excellent communication and problem-solving skills. Track record of achieving exceptional results for clients and working with my peers to increase overall team performance.

## **SKILLS**

- HTML5 / CSS3
- Active Directory
- Exchange Support
- Bootstrap
- React.js
- MongoDB / MySQL
- Git / Github Web Development
- Hardware install / server racks / full computer construction and repair

- JavaScript / jQuery /Java
- SCCM
- Office 365
- Express.js
- Node.js
- Command Line
- Windows 7, 10 and office suite
- Team Leadership and Management
- Sales Customer and Client relationships

## **EXPERIENCE**

#### **HUNTON ANDREWS KURTH LLP**

IT Support Ctr Coordinator | Richmond, United States, VA, United States | February 2014 - Current

- Provided onsite, remote technical support, and coaching for firm supported applications and services such as Office 2010 2016, Adobe acrobat, Nuance PDF, iManage, and Litera products.
- Problem resolution for high profile issues serving demanding users and clients.
- Managed client accounts, passwords, network access, and application installations using Active Directory and System Center Configuration Manager.
- Deployed and configured firm software to mobile devices using AirWatch.
- Experienced in Service Now ticketing environment to accurately document and escalate incidents and requests in a timely manner.
- Create, maintain, and enter information into our internal I.T.

- Knowledge base for fixes / resolutions, general documentation and SOP.
- Collaborated with neighboring teams on multiple projects to develop a greater understanding of their roles and responsibilities and to reduce turn-around time.
- Organized, inventoried, and managed firm assets and assisted with hardware deployments.
- Traveled to support multiple out-of-state office consolidations and hardware setups.

# GEED SQUAD ADVANCED, BEST BUY

Repair Agent | Richmond, United States, VA, United States | February 2014 - August 2016

- Accurate interpenetrate client description of the problem to find accurate solutions.
- Diagnose, troubleshoot and repair software and operating systems on client personal Desktop and laptops.
- Assembled, maintained, and repaired system hardware.
- Held accountable for accurate notes and client communications.
- Fully Assembled, maintained, and repaired system hardware.

# GEEK SQUAD DEPUTY OF COUNTER INTELLIGENCE, BEST BUY

Manager | Richmond, United States, VA, United States | August 2009 - February 2014

- Responsible for all operations of the in-store Geek Squad Businesses and Brand representation.
- Develop Department Business Plan and execution including Car Audio install bay.
- Hiring, training, scheduling and development of over 20 employees.
- Responsible for all Client interactions, including corporate complaints.
- Managed and accountable for paperwork and legal documentation regarding the paid for services.
- Perform hardware and software repair/upgrades, virus removals, network repair and client consulting.
- Lead and develop district wide training and best practices.

#### SHOCKOE PROPERTIES LLC

Maintenance Technician | Richmond, United States, VA, United States | June 2006 - August 2011

- Oversee all operations concerning the common areas of the building.
- Supervise cleanliness and security of the buildings.
- Daily interfacing with tenants and owners.
- Scheduling and supervising contractors, vendors and construction.
- Generated information for management regarding building efficiency regarding cost of repairs, overall maintenance, construction and upgrades.

#### JOHN TYLER COMMUNITY COLLEGE - MIDLOTHIAN CAMPUS

Math and English Tutor | VA, United States | August 2005 - June 2006

- Students taking freshman and sophomore college level Math and English.
- Scheduled appointments, fielded phone calls and filed paperwork.

# **EDUCATION**

# FULL STACK WEB DEVELOPMENT CERTIFICATE: FULL STACK MERN WEB DEVELOPTMENT

University of Richmond

Richmond, VA, United States | 2020

Full Stack MERN Web Developmental: Mongo DB, Express JS, React JS/ Redux and Node JS. Among these technologies Mongo DB is a database system, Node JS is a back-end runtime environment, Express JS is a back-end web framework and React is a front-end framework.

Personal Study in math Virginia Commonwealth University VA, United States | 2016

#### ASSOCIATE OF SCIENCE

John Tyler Community College Richmond, VA, United States | 2009

#### **ASSOCIATE OF ARTS**

John Tyler Community College VA, United States | 2009

# HIGH SCHOOL DIPLOMA

Midlothian High School

VA, United States | 2005